

Venezuelan - Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

(+1) 407-601.9438 victorteppa@gmail.com Kissimmee, FL. 34744

https://vteppaweb.github.io/resume/index.html

Professional Summary

I am an Information Technology professional with over 8 years of overseas creativity and

passionate experience with a high level of academic education based on my bachelor degree

in computer science.

Determination to learn new technologies, proactive attitude, written and verbal

communication are just some of my key strengths, which will make me a very competitive

candidate.

Others key strengths that I possess include, but are not limited to, the following:

My knowledge on life cycle development software.

• I am a self-starter, bilingual and an excellent team worker.

Responsive web application design.

My passion and ability to create apps and website solutions.

Front End and Back End web programming experience.

• Always willing to learn and stay tune with the latest technologies.

Knowledge of SEO, KPI's, SSRS and Google Analytics.

It would be great to have the opportunity that allow me to have a professional development

and continue my career in this wonderful field.

Venezuelan - Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

Experience

Front End Web Developer

GeoSnapShot Sydney, Australia. Sep, 2015 – Sep, 2017.

- Maintenance of the web pages look & feel.
- Evaluation of new changes under new web templates.
- Create responsive HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript web templates.
- Work on changes using (GIT-HUB, BOOTSTRAP, HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, Sublime Text Editor).

Web Application Developer

MS21Consulting. Venezuela. April 2012 – Jan, 2013.

- Analyse, design, development and maintenance of the desktop, web applications, web services and windows services implemented.
- Responsible for the development of Front End and Back End of the projects.

Analysts & Web Developer App

NewTech Sistemas, C.A. Venezuela. Nov, 2009 – March, 2012.

Design, development and implementation of web applications to supervise and monitoring the products samples of the sales department of multinational 3M Manufacture Company.
 Software Used: IBM I-Series AS/400, Microsoft Internet Explorer 7-8, Mozilla Firefox 4.0, Microsoft Office Suite, IBM Lotus Notes 8.5, Macromedia Dreamweaver, Adobe Photoshop, Visual Studio.Net 2003/2010, Microsoft Project, Reporting Services 2007, QlikView 9.0, Cisco IP Communicator.

Web Application Developer

Grupo SMS, C.A. Venezuela. July, 2007 – Oct, 2009.

• Design and Development of new web applications. The most important projects developed using this programs were:



Venezuelan - Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

- 1. Creation of a Microsoft SharePoint web application to supervise and monitoring the workflow of the process of all departments of the multinational company: Movistar Telefonica Venezuela. Project duration: 10 months.
- 2. Collaboration in the design and development of the Look & Feel of web applications.
- **Software Used:** Internet Explorer 6-7, Mozilla Firefox, Microsoft Office, Macromedia Dreamweaver, Adobe Photoshop, Visual Studio.Net 2005, Microsoft Project, Microsoft Reporting Services 2005, Microsoft SQL Server 2005, Microsoft SharePoint Server and SharePoint Designer 2007.
- **Architectures:** 3-Tier, MVC and SOA.

Multimedia eLearning Developer

The eLearning Solutions, C.A. Venezuela. Sep, 2005 – May, 2007.

- Collaborate with the creative illustrator and design department.
- Develop the learning platform with the supplied files and tools using Macromedia Flash and coding all characters movements.
- Work in the design and development of the Look & Feel in all projects.

Venezuelan – Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

Education:

Nueva Esparta University.

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science. Caracas – Venezuela. 2006.

Courses & Seminaries:

Udemy.com

Complete ASP.NET MVC course in C# Learn basics of MVC and how to build fast and secure web apps with ASP.NET MVC 5. 2021.

Udemy.com

ASP.NET MVC + Entity Framework 2021.

Coursera.org by Google Cloud.

Organizational Change and Culture for Adopting Google Cloud. Business Transformation with Google Cloud. 2020 - 2021.

Coursera.org by UCDAVIS University of California.

SEO - Search Engine Optimization.

SEO Optimization / Fundamentals / Best Practices / Advanced Content and Social Tactics to Optimize SEO / Optimizing a Website for Search. 2020.

Coursera.org by the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology.

Front End Web UI Frameworks and Tools.
Bootstrap, Angular, NodeJs, MongoDB, JQuery, NPM, Lite-Server, Json, Github, CSS Pre-processors Less and Sass.
2020.

Coursera Project Network.

Position Elements on a Page with CSS. HTML5, CSS3. 2020.

Coursera.org by University of Michigan.

Web Design, Development and Coding. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap and Advanced Responsive Design. 2020.

TAFE Ultimo, New South Wales.

Web Design & Development (Certificate III and IV). Sydney, Australia. 2014 – 2015

> Victor Rafael Teppa Delfino

Venezuelan – Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

Navitas English Institute.

Academic English level 2 and 3. Sydney, Australia. 2014

Navitas English Institute.

IELTS Preparation Course. Sydney, Australia. 2013

Navitas English Institute.

General English Course. Brisbane, Australia. 2013

Navitas English Institute.

FCE – Cambridge First Certificate English. Brisbane, Australia. 2013

Centro Integral de Comunicación Visual.

Adobe After Effects 7.0 Pro

This course was instructed by an approved member of the Adobe Authorized Training Provider in Venezuela. 2006.

Centro Integral de Comunicación Visual.

Macromedia Fireworks MX 2004

This course was instructed by a fully-accredited member of the Macromedia Authorized Training Partner in Venezuela. 2004.

Centro Integral de Comunicación Visual.

Adobe Flash MX 2004 Advanced Development (Action Script). This course was instructed by a fully-accredited member of the Macromedia Authorized Training Partner in Venezuela. 2003.

CASE Institute.

Web Design. Caracas - Venezuela 2001.

Instituto de Capacitación Técnica KEYS.

Networks Seminary. Caracas - Venezuela 2000.

> Victor Rafael Teppa Delfino

Venezuelan - Bachelor Degree in Computing Science

Luisa Cáceres de Arismendi Institute.
 Technical repair and maintenance of personal computers.
 Caracas - Venezuela
 1997.

Hard Skills:

- Life Cycle of Web Applications.
- Advanced Responsive Web Design.
- SEO, KPI's, Reporting Services and Google Analytics.
- Front End Web UI / UX Frameworks.
- HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap4, Angular.
- Version control systems GitHub / BitBucket.
- SQL-Server Databases.
- VS.NET, MVC, ASP.NET, C#.NET
- CMS: DNN / WordPress / Sitecore / Microsoft SharePoint Designer.
- LMS Learning Management Systems Experience (eLearning).
- Adobe & Macromedia Suite: Dreamweaver / Fireworks / Photoshop / After Effects / Flash.
- Basic Graphic Design, Video and Audio Edition.

Soft Skills:

- Bilingual: English / Spanish.
- Multicultural and Open Minded.
- CPR and First Aid Certification.
- Fitness and Personal Trainer Certifications.
- Culinary Skills.